http://www.sportrx.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode

$60 off any Order $300+ | Code: HOLIDAY60 SHOP NOW20% off Nike Prescription Eyewear | Code: NIKE20 SHOP NOW50% off a Second Pair of Maui Jim Rx Eyeglasses | Code: MAUIBOGO SHOP NOWUse Your FSA Dollars Before They Expire 12/31 LEARN MORE
PRIVACY POLICYThis Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from sportrx.com.PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECTLike most websites, when you visit sportrx.com, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the site, and information about how you interact with the site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”We collect Device Information using the following technologies:“Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit all about cookies.“Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.“Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.Additionally, when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through sportrx.com, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information, email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.”=When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:Communicate with you, improve customer service, and screen orders for potential risk or fraud.HOW DO WE USE YOUR DEVICE INFORMATION?We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the site, and to assess the success of our marketing campaigns).SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONSportRx does not sell, share, or disclose any personal information with any third partiesSHARING YOUR DEVICE INFORMATIONWe share your Device Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here .BEHAVIORAL MARKETINGAs described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page here.You can opt out of targeted advertising by: FACEBOOK - SETTINGS GOOGLE - SETTINGS BING - SETTINGSAdditionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal here.DO NOT TRACKPlease note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.YOUR RIGHTSIf you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.DATA RETENTIONWhen you place an order through sportrx.com, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.MINORSThe Site is not intended for individuals under the age of 18.CHANGESWe may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.CONTACT USFor more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at info@sportrx.com
Chat
